Guide to the Frank S. Hatch correspondence with F. C. Blank
Yale University Arts Library
Frank S. Hatch correspondence with F. C. Blank
1926-1936
BKP 136
Yale University Arts Library
0.125
(1 box)
The collection contains correspondence between Frank S. Hatch of Longmeadow, MA, and the bookplate designer Frederick Charles Blank of Boston.
Hatch, Frank S.
Blank, F. C.
Associated Materials
For additional correspondence by Frank S. Hatch, see also the Collection of the Frank S. Hatch bookplate designed and engraved by Alfred J. Downey (Call # BKP 115).
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Acquired by purchase, 2013.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains correspondence between Frank S. Hatch of Longmeadow, MA, and the bookplate designer Frederick Charles Blank of Boston. The collection also contains two Christmas cards and a preliminary pencil sketch by Blank for Hatch's angling bookplate as well as one letter signed by Marian Hatch. In addition to the transactions between artist and patron, the letters also include discussion of bookplate collecting and offers of exchange.
Arrangement
Arranged chronologically.
Bookplates; Correspondence; Hatch, Frank S.
- Correspondence, 1926-1936
  Scope and Contents
  All letters are addressed to F. C. Blank and authored by Frank S. Hatch with the exception of one letter by his wife, Marian Hatch.
  - TLS to Mr. Frederick Blank, March 13, 1926; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - TLS to Mr. Frederick C. Blank, March 20, 1926; 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - TLS to Mr. F.C. Blank, March 29, 1926; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - TLS to Mr. F.C. Blank, August 16, 1926; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - TLS to Mr. Frederick C. Blank, October 11, 1926; 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - ALS and cards, [November 19, 1926 ]; 3 items (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Includes ALS to Mr. Blank from Marian Hatch; 2 Christmas cards designed by Blank for Frank and Marian Hatch (1 black-and-white; 1 hand-colored).
  - TLS to Mr. F.C. Blank, November 29, 1926; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - TLS to Mr. F.C. Blank, December 16, 1926; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - TLS to Mr. Frederick C. Blank, December 30, 1926; 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - TLS to Mr. Frederick C. Blank, May 29, 1928; 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - TLS to Mr. Frederick C. Blank, June 12, 1928; 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - TLS to Mr. Frederick C. Blank, November 2, 1928; 2 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Includes pencil sketch of preliminary design for Hatch's angling bookplate designed by Blank.
  - TLS to Mr. F.C. Blank, December 31, 1935; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - TLS to Mr. F.C. Blank, January 16, 1936; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - TLS to Mr. F.C. Blank, January 23, 1936; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - TLS to Mr. Frederick C. Blank, January 29, 1936; 1 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - TLS to Mr. F.C. Blank, February 8, 1936; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - TLS to Mr. F.C. Blank, February 18, 1936; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - TLS to Mr. F.C. Blank, May 26, 1936; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - TLS to Mr. F.C. Blank, October 19, 1936; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - TLS to Mr. F.C. Blank, October 27, 1936; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - TLS to Mr. H. [sic] C. Blank, November 3, 1936; 1 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - TLS to Mr. F.C. Blank, November 13, 1936; 1 item (Box 1, Folder 23)